[음악]
Uh Uh Too Spicy
You want my A to the Z
But you won't get it, not a chance
Take your pick, Sweet or Freak?
What’s hiding underneath (I see)
Sittin' on the fence, Oh, ain't got a chance
Nah You won’t get it
No No, You won’t get it
I say
Pulled in in a blink of an eye, You'll be mine (Mine)
Get closer Can cross my borderline (Line Line Line)
Every day got you bored
Gonna throw down some fun traps
Jump on in
Just right now
'Cause I’m too Spicy for your heart
Ring the fire alarm
You tiptoe into my heart
향신료 밑에 숨어 있는 것
I'm too Spicy
While the fire spreads
[음악]
In that very moment
Finding another part of me
I’m too Spicy too too
I’m too Spicy
Don't Stop, don't be scared
나 자신
Bang Bang, shout it out
I’m too Spicy Yeah I’m too Spicy
You know that I
Don't Stop, be brave now
Next step, Myself
[음악]
I’m too Spicy
Too Spicy too too
Tell me what you see
[음악]
When you look at me
'Cause I am a 10 out of 10 honestly
[음악]
A different energy, this Move
Overpowering Groove
[음악]
But you keep wasting your time Dude
Don't chase me, I'm warning you
[음악]
Erase me, run far away
Hey, you get it now?
[음악]
I was born Bad I'm so bad honestly
So bad
Want it all, gonna Call you mine now (Mine)
If you gonna dip, Don’t cross my borderline (Line Line Line)
Every day the same old, same old
Time now to toss that Rule
Ain't hard to do
Just right now
'Cause I’m too Spicy for your heart
Ring the fire alarm
[음악]
You tiptoe into my heart
레벨 2
I'm too Spicy
장치
[음악]
While the fire spreads
In that very moment
Discovering yet another me
I’m too Spicy too too
[음악]
I’m too Spicy
Ready? Uh
[음악]
Gimme the next level, Next Next Next
독특한
One of a kind
[음악]
Beyond our limits, Wow Wow Wow
That’s Right
매운 것
'Cause I’m too Spicy for your heart
Ring the fire alarm
Completed another challenge
[음악]
I'm too Spicy
It's your time to change
[음악]
Right this moment
Finding another part of me
I’m too Spicy too too
[음악]
I’m too Spicy
Don't Stop, don't be scared
Bang Bang, shout it out
무슨 일이야
I’m too Spicy Yeah I’m too Spicy
You know that I
Don't Stop, be brave now
Next step, Myself
[음악]
I’m too Spicy I’m too Spicy
I’m too Spicy too too I’m too Spicy
[음악]
'Cause I
Oh Yeah
[음악]
Yeah I’m too Spicy for your heart
(Yeah I’m too Spicy for your heart)
Finally comes the feeling of Joy (Enjoy joy joy joy)
[음악]
Yeah I’m too Spicy for your heart
I’m too Spicy too too
[음악]
I’m too Spicy
For you
고마워요