Armageddon
Shoot
Imma get ’em
Watch Uh Uh
Imma bite back Uh
짙은 어둠이
深い暗闇が
When the thick darkness
막아설 땐 Uh
立ちはだかる時には Uh
Stops ya, Uh
한 걸음 앞으로
一歩前へ
One step forward
날아든 It’s bad
舞い込んだ It’s bad
Swoop, It's bad
사라진 Feedback
消えた Feedback
Gone, Feedback
시작된 Code black Uh
始まった Code black Uh
Hit it, Code black Uh
깊어가
更けていく
Getting deeper
혼란스러운 밤
入り乱れる夜
This chaotic night
악몽은 또 짙게 번져가
悪夢はまた色濃く滲んでいく
And sticky thick nightmare creeps
뭔갈 숨기려고 해
何かを隠そうとしている
Tryna hide something
I got it, I got it
혼돈을 타고
カオスに紛れて
Riding in on the chaos, then
덮쳐, killing like
襲いかかる Killing like
Strike, Killing like
Bang chitty bang
Bang chitty bang bang
’Cause I wanna see
I wanna see truly
Bang chitty bang
Bang chitty bang bang
나에게 더 가까이 와라
私に近づいてきて 近づいてきて
Come to me, closer, closer
Imma get it
Done (Aw wayo wayo)
널 향해 겨눠 Get it, gone
君に向かって狙いを定める Get it, gone
Aimed at ya, Get it, gone
(Aw wayo wayo)
이젠 널 끝내 Better run
もう君を仕留める Better run
Now I finish ya, Better run
끝을 모르는 너와 나, you gonna, gonna
(終わりを知らない君と私 You gonna, gonna)
(You and I we know no end, You gonna, gonna)
깨트려 거침없이 Done
ぶち壊す 躊躇せずに Done
Smash it no doubt, Done
(Go way up, way up)
Full shot pull it up Armageddon
Imma get ’em
Shoot
Hey Ya Uh~
또 다른 나 Uh uh
もう一人の私
My alter ego
>릴 막지 마 Uh~
私たちを止めないで
Don't block our flow
We never play nice
Shoot
완벽한 Pair
完璧な Pair
A perfect Pair
넌 똑같은 soul
君はそっくりな Soul
You're my identical Soul
Three to get ready
우린 shoot and go
私たちは Shoot and go
We're Shoot and go
겁 없이 누벼
何も恐れず駆け巡る
Roam unafraid
날 이끄는 Way
私を導く Way
Leading me is the Way
Bang chitty bang
Bang chitty bang bang
Yes I’m gonna see
I’m gonna see, want it
Bang chitty bang
Bang chitty bang bang
답이 들려와, 들려와
答えが聞こえてくる 聞こえてくる
The answer, I hear it, I hear it
Imma get it
Done
(Aw wayo wayo)
널 향해 겨눠, get it, gone
君に向かって狙いを定める Get it, gone
Aimed at ya, Get it, gone
(Aw wayo wayo)
이젠 널 끝내, better run
もう君を仕留める Better run
Now I finish ya, Better run
끝을 모르는 너와 나, you gonna, gonna
(終わりを知らない君と私 You gonna, gonna)
(You and I we know no end, You gonna, gonna)
깨트려 거침없이 Done
ぶち壊す 躊躇せずに Done
Smash it no douobt, Done
(Go way up, way up)
Full shot pull it up Armageddon
Imma get ’em
또 어둠을 몰아내고
また暗闇を追い払って
Drive off the darkness once more
시작을 꽃피운 너와 나의 story
始まりを咲かせた君と私の Story
And so it flowers this Story of us
더 완벽해진 우리
もっと完璧になった私たち
You and me, even more flawless
정의해 이젠
定義する これからは
Now define it
나만의 Complete
私だけの Complete
My personal definition of Complete
내 모든 걸 이끌어
私のすべてを導いていく
I shall lead every part of me
Do it all myself
완전한 나를 이뤄내
完全な私を作り出す
At last complete myself
(Drop)
Throw it back, throw it back, throw it back
Born like a queen
Born like a king Ya
Throw it back, throw it back, throw it back
불러
呼んで
Sing it
Imma get ’em
Done aespa!
(Aw wayo wayo)
널 향해 겨눠 Get it, gone aespa!
君に向かって狙いを定める Get it, gone
Aimed at ya, Get it, gone
(Aw wayo wayo)
이젠 널 끝내, better run
もう君を仕留める Better run
Now I finish ya, Better run
끝을 모르는 너와 나 You gonna, gonna
(終わりを知らない君と私 You gonna, gonna)
(You and I we know no end, You gonna, gonna)
깨트려 거침없이 Done aespa!
ぶち壊す 躊躇せずに Done
Smash it no doubt, Done
(Go way up, way up)
Full shot pull it up Armageddon
Armageddon
(Aw wayo wayo wayo Warning all night long)
(Aw wayo wayo)
끝과 시작의
終わりと始まりの
For both the end and the beginning
Armageddon