Ya Ya I’m the Drama aespa
Ziggy ziggy zag I’m new
Cause I go biggie biggie bad It’s true
날카로운 눈 안에 비친 Toxic
鋭い目の中に映った Toxic
Sharp eye, inside it's Toxic
내 본능을 당겨 Zoom
私の本能を引き寄せる Zoom
Zoom in, pull on my instincts
Hold up, What? Oh my god
You say, what? 다쳐 넌
You say, What? 怪我するよ 君は
You say, What? You gon' get hurt
You better watch out
우린 이미 거센 Boom
私たちはもう激しい Boom
We already that big, tough Boom
달려가고 있어 Vroom
駆けつけている Vroom
Racing with that big, bad Vroom
I li-li like me when I roll
Li-li-like me when I’m savage
Li-li-like me when I go
Li-li-likie when I baddest
Hold up 빛을 따라서
Hold up 光を追いかけて
Hold up, chasing lights
달아 다 다 달려나가 Run
月よ　走っていけ Run
Racing lights, run, run on, Run
Go Finally Ra ta ta ta
다음 세계를 열어 난
次の世界を切り開く 私は
Open up a new world, boom-ta-da
1, 2 It’s time to go
후회 없어 난
後悔はしない 私は
Regrets, ain't got 'em
맞서 난 깨버렸지
立ち向かって私はぶち破ったわ
Square up, I break 'em
날 따라서 움직일 Rules
私に従って動く Rules
Rules, they gon' follow me
손끝으로세상을 두드려 움직여
指先で世界を叩いて動かす
Tap my finger and watch the world move
Yeah I’m coming
I bring I bring
all the Drama-ma-ma-ma Hey Hey
I bring Drama-ma-ma-ma Hey Hey
With my girls in the back
Girls in the back
Drama
Trauma-ma-ma-ma Hey Hey
I break Trauma-ma-ma-ma Hey Hey
With MY WORLD in the back
나로 시작되는 Drama
私で始まる Drama
It starts with me, Drama
(All that)
Drama-ma-ma-ma
(Bring it that)
With my girls in the back
Girls in the back Yeah
I break
Trauma-ma-ma-ma
(We them)
With MY WORLD in the back
나로 시작되는 Drama
私で始まる Drama
It starts with me, Drama
Drama-ma-ma-ma
Drama-ma-ma-ma (3, 2, 1)
Drama-ma-ma
You know I’ve been kind of like
1, 2, 3 깜짝 놀랄 다음 Scenе
1, 2, 3 びっくりするような次の Scene
1, 2, 3, cue that jump-scare Scene
키를 거머쥔
キーを握りしめる
Who's got the key?
주인공은 나
主人公は私
Main character, that's me
4, 3, 2 Going down
쉽게 Through
簡単に Through
Breezin' Through
Déjà vu 같이
Deja Vu みたいに
Just like Deja Vu
그려지는 이미지
描かれていくイメージ
They picture my image
날 굳이 막지 말아
私を止めようとしないで
Don't try to stop me
이건 내 Drama Drama
これは私の Drama
This is my Drama
도발은 굳이 안 막아
挑発は敢えて止めないわ
Pull up if you wanna
Uh, I’m a stunner
1, 2 It’s time to go
타오르는 날 (타는 날)
燃え上がる私を (燃える私を)
I ignite (I shine bright)
느껴 난 And I love it
感じる 私は And I love it
Feelin' it, And I love it
새로워지는 Rules
新しくなる Rules
New game, new Rules
난 눈을 떠 (두 눈을 떠)
私は目を開ける (両目を開ける)
I open my eyes (open my eyes)
(넌) 알아 (Now)
始まったことに (君は) 気付く (Now)
Game on, (you) know it (Now)
It’s coming
I bring I bring all the
Drama-ma-ma-ma Hey Hey
I bring Drama-ma-ma-ma Hey Hey
With my girls in the back
Girls in the back
Drama
Trauma-ma-ma-ma Hey Hey
I break Trauma-ma-ma-ma Hey Hey
With MY WORLD in the back
나로 시작되는 Drama
私で始まる Drama
It starts with me, Drama
Into the REAL WORLD
다가온 Climax
迫ってきた Climax
Climax on deck
두려워하지 마
恐れないで
Don't be afraid
You and I
함께 써 내려가는 Story
一緒に書いていく Story
Together we write this Story
날 가로막았던 No
私の前に立ちはだかっていた No
Past hurdles, No more
한계를 뛰어 넘어 Every day
限界を飛び越える Every day
Push boundaries Every day
Oh Imma make it my way
Out of the way Yeah
I bring I bring all the
Drama-ma-ma-ma Hey Hey
I bring Drama-ma-ma-maHey Hey
With my girls in the back
Girls in the back
Drama
Trauma-ma-ma-ma Hey Hey
I break Trauma-ma-ma-ma Hey Hey
With MY WORLD in the back
나와 함께하는 Drama
私と一緒に作っていく Drama
It stays with me, Drama
You know, I’m savage
거침없는 baddest
よどみないBaddest
Unstoppable, Baddest
나를 둘러싼 thrill
私を取り巻く Thrill
All wrapped in Thrill
거친 여정 속의 Drama
荒い旅路の中にある Drama
Bumpy off-road Drama
(Drama-ma-ma)
내가 깨트릴 모든 Trauma
私がぶち破るすべての Trauma
I'll break this cycle of Trauma
(Drama-ma-ma)
지금 시작되는 Drama
今始まる Drama
It starts now, Drama
Ya aespa Ya Drama 너로 시작될 MY Drama
Ya Ya 君から始まる MY Drama
Ya Ya, It starts with you, MY Drama