A hot mess, hot mess
息吹きかけて Listen up
숨을 내쉬고 잘 들어 봐
Blow it up Listen up
とびきり“らしさ”で Fill it up
특출나게 “나다움”으로 채우겠어
With my own style Fill it up
Iʼm a troublemaker, troublemaker Yuh!
Whatʼs so funny, funny, honey?
I got Ahh your attention
Sing loud, loud loud loud
あっという間に Time’s up
눈 깜짝할 새에 시간 다 됐어
In a blink of an eye Time’s up
Open your blind blind mind mind
Everybody waits for me
Make the sensation
どんな形でも Okay Okay
어떤 형태라도 Okay
In any shape or form is okay
ひたすら On my way
한결같이 내 길을 걸어
Single mindedly on my way
Take it slowly
Ainʼt no worry
Dancing with the flames
I'm a hot mess, hot mess
描いてきた Story Never hesitate
그려 왔던 스토리 망설이지 않아
Story I’ve been drawing Never hesitate
I'm a hot mess, hot mess
So if U LIKE it,
I can take you to MY WORLD Hwi Hwi
I am the one (Hot)
I am the best (Hot)
止まらない もう
멈추지 않아 이제
I won’t stop anymore
I am the one (Hot)
And now my turn (Hot)
Yeah, Iʼm a hot mess
画期的登場シーン
획기적인 등장 신
Groundbreaking appearance
Shake it Mix it 目を惹く My style
흔들고 섞으며 눈길을 끄는 내 스타일
Shake it Mix it My eye-catching style
目が眩むほど光る Dimension
아찔할 정도로 눈부신 디멘션
Dazzling dimension
Feel it coming now,
feel it taking over
I’ll blow ur mind mind like all the time time
潜めた ænergy 夢のDesigner
숨은 ænergy 꿈의 Designer
Hidden ænergy Dream Designer
Now, Now oh yeah, that’s right right
So come on
いつも攻めてる Show you ma attitude
항상 과감하게
Always daring Show you ma attitude
どんな形でも Okay Okay
어떤 형태라도 Okay
In any shape or form is okay
ひたすら On my way
한결같이 내 길을 걸어
Single mindedly on my way
Take it slowly
Ainʼt no worry
Dancing with the flames
I'm a hot mess, hot mess
描いてきた Story Never hesitate
그려 왔던 스토리 망설이지 않아
Story I’ve been drawing Never hesitate
I'm a hot mess, hot mess
So if U LIKE it,
I can take you to MY WORLD Hwi Hwi
I never lay low, never lay low
U watch me glow glow,
watch me glow glow
Drama has begun This is not fiction
Ready or Not
Make it hot hot, make it hot hot
Baby Iʼm on fire, Iʼm on fire
Fire Ah Ooh
I'm a hot mess, hot mess
描いてきた Story Never hesitate
그려 왔던 스토리 망설이지 않아
Story I’ve been drawing Never hesitate
I'm a hot mess, hot mess
So if U LIKE it,
I can take you to MY WORLD Hwi Hwi
I am the one (Hot)
I am the best (Hot)
止まらない もう (I am the one)
멈추지 않아 이제
I won’t stop anymore (I am the one)
I am the one (Hot)
And now my turn (Hot)
Yeah, Iʼm a hot mess
Know you want it some more
時空を飛び越え Believe in yourself
시공을 뛰어넘어 네 자신을 믿어 봐
Beyond time and space Believe in yourself
Know you want it some more
開かれた世界
열린 세계
Open world
Hot mess, hot mess