KARINA GISELLE Uh Uh WINTER NINGNING Too Spicy aespa
You want my A to the Z
But you won't 어림없지
But you won't 無理に決まってる
But you won't get it, not a chance
맞혀봐 sweet 또는 freak
当ててみて Sweet または Freak
Take your pick, Sweet or Freak?
What’s hiding underneath (I see)
>망설이듯 간 보는 너 기회는 없어 Oh
躊躇うように探りを入れる君　チャンスはない　Oh
Sittin' on the fence, Oh, ain't got a chance
>Nah You won’t get it
No No You won’t get it
I say
깜빡 한순간 끌어당겨 you'll be mine (Mine)
ぱっと一瞬で引き寄せる You'll be mine (Mine)
Pulled in in a blink of an eye, You'll be mine (Mine)
살짝 다가와 can cross my borderline (L-l-line)
そっと近づいてきて Can cross my borderline (L-l-line)
Get closer Can cross my borderline (L-l-line)
널 따분하게 했던 Every day (Day)
君を退屈にさせていた Every day
Every day got you bored
흥미로운 덫을 던져줄게 (Play)
面白い罠を投げてあげるわ
Gonna throw down some fun traps
뛰어들어 봐 just right now
飛び込んでみて just right now
Jump on in Just right now
'Cause I’m too Spicy for your heart aespa
Ring the fire alarm
심장을 파고들어 넌
心に入り込む 君は
You tiptoe into my heart
I'm too Spicy
번지는 자극 속에 넌
滲む刺激の中で君は
While the fire spreads
바로 그 순간
ちょうどその瞬間
In that very moment
또 다른 나를 발견해
また違う私を発見する
Finding another part of me
I’m too Spicy too too
I’m too Spicy
Don't stop, 겁내지 마 Hey
Don't Stop 怖がらないで
Don't Stop, don't be scared
Bang Bang 외쳐봐
Bang Bang 叫んでみて
Bang Bang, shout it out
I’m too Spicy Yeah I’m too Spicy
You know that I
Don't stop, 용기 내 봐 Hey
Don't Stop 勇気を出してみて
Don't Stop, be brave now
Next step, Myself
I’m too Spicy
Too Spicy too too
Tell me what you see SEE
When you look at me ME
'Cause I am a 10 out of 10 honestly
기세가 다른 Move
勢いが違う Move
A different energy, this Move
널 압도하는 Groove
君を圧倒する Groove
Overpowering Groove
But you keep wasting your time Dude
Don't chase mе 경고해 난
Don't chase me 警告する 私は
Don't chase me, I'm warning you
Erase me 멀리 달아나
Erase me 遠くに逃げて
Erase me, run far away
Hey 이젠 알겠니
Hey もう分かる？
Hey, you get it now?
원래부터 bad, I'm so bad honеstly
元々 Bad I’m so bad honestly
I was born Bad I'm so bad honestly
So bad
전부 가질래 지금부턴 call you mine (Mine)
全部私のものにする これからは Call you mine (Mine)
Want it all, gonna Call you mine now (Mine)
도망칠 거면 don't cross my borderline (L-l-line)
逃げるなら Don’t cross my borderline (Line Line Line)
If you gonna dip, Don’t cross my borderline (Line Line Line)
늘 뻔하기만 했던 Every day day
いつもありきたりだった Every day
Every day the same old, same old
이제 그만 rule을 벗어날 때 Play
もう Ruleから外れるとき
Time now to toss that Rule
어렵지 않아 just right now
難しくない Just right now
Ain't hard to do Just right now
'Cause I’m too Spicy for your heart aespa
Ring the fire alarm
심장을 파고들어 넌
心に入り込む 君は
You tiptoe into my heart
I'm too Spicy
번지는 자극 속에 넌
滲む刺激の中で君は
While the fire spreads
바로 그 순간
ちょうどその瞬間
In that very moment
또 다른 나를 발견해
また違う私を発見する
Discovering yet another me
I’m too Spicy too too
I’m too Spicy
Ready? Uh
좀 더 강도를 높여 다음, 다음, 다음
もう少し強度を上げて 次、次、次
Gimme the next level, Next Next Next
One of a kind
우린 한계를 앞서 Wow Wow Wow
私たちは限界の先を行く Wow Wow Wow
Beyond our limits, Wow Wow Wow
That’s Right
'Cause I’m too Spicy for your heart aespa
Ring the fire alarm
새로운 도전 끝에 넌
新しい挑戦の末に君は
Completed another challenge
I'm too Spicy
변화할 시간이야 넌
変化する時間だよ 君は
It's your time to change
지금 이 순간
今この瞬間
Right this moment
또 다른 나를 찾아내
また違う私を見つけ出す
Finding another part of me
I’m too Spicy too too
I’m too Spicy
Don't stop, 겁내지 마 Hey
Don't Stop 怖がらないで
Don't Stop, don't be scared
Bang Bang 외쳐봐
Bang Bang 叫んでみて
Bang Bang, shout it out
I’m too Spicy Yeah I’m too Spicy
You know that I
Don't stop 용기 내 봐 Hey
Don't Stop 勇気を出してみて
Don't Stop, be brave now
Next step, Myself
I’m too Spicy I’m too Spicy
I’m too Spicy too too I’m too Spicy
'Cause I
Oh Yeah
Yeah I’m too Spicy for your heart
(Yeah I’m too Spicy for your heart)
마침내 번져오는 joy (Enjoy, joy, joy, joy)
ついに滲んでくる Joy (Enjoy joy joy joy)
Finally comes the feeling of Joy (Enjoy joy joy joy)
Yeah I’m too Spicy for your heart
I’m too Spicy too too
I’m too Spicy
For you