One look give ‘em Whiplash Whiplash!
Beat drop with a big flash big flash!
집중해 좀 더 Think fast Think fast
集中して もっと Think fast
C'mon, focus Think fast
이유 넌 이해 못 해
理由 君には分からない
They're reasons you'll never understand
왜 이제야 Know I did that did that
どうして今さら Know I did that
Why at last Know I did that
Day 1 know I been bad been bad
Don’t stop 흔들린 채
Don’t stop 揺さぶられたまま
Don’t stop Still shook
무리해도 Can’t touch that Can’t touch that
無理しても Can’t touch that
Goin' too hard, yet Can’t touch that
Under pressure, body sweating
Can you focus aespa!
어디서나 거침없어
どこでだってためらわずに
Wherever I am can't stop me
I’m the coldest aespa!
오직 나만이
ただ私だけが
I'm the only
이 판을 바꿀 Changer
この構図を変える Changer
Game-Changer bringin' the new era
Just close your eyes,
breathe in and visualize
One look give ‘em Whiplash Whiplash
Beat drop with a big flash big flash
집중해 좀 더 Think fast Think fast
集中して もっと Think fast
C'mon, focus Think fast
이유 넌 이해 못 해
理由 君には分からない
They're reasons you'll never understand
왜 이제야 Know I did that did that
どうして今さら Know I did that
Why at last Know I did that
Day 1 know I been bad been bad
Don’t stop 흔들린 채
Don’t stop 揺さぶられたまま
Don’t stop Still shook
무리해도
無理しても
Goin' too hard, yet
Can’t touch that Can't touch that Can't touch that
Whip-Whiplash
One look give ‘em Whiplash
Fancy
이건 참 화려해
これって本当派手だね
This so glitzy
It’s glowing and it’s flashy
알아 적당함이 뭔지
分かってる 適度とは何か
Keep it just right, I know it
Keep it classy
따라 하지
マネする
Cats gon' copy
넌 또 하나부터 열까지
君はまた一から十まで
One idea, two, then the whole look
아닌척하지 Yeah aespa!
白を切る Yeah
Then deny it Yeah
Under pressure, body sweating
Can you focus aespa!
I deliver, I can promise
I’m the coldest aespa!
외면해도 소용없지 Don't you blow it
無視しても無馱だよ
Head in the sand won't solve it
Just close your eyes,
breathe in and visualize
시작되는 순간 끝나버린 판단
始まる瞬間 終わってしまった判断
The moment it begins Verdict is in
기횐 오직 One time
チャンスはたった One time
Opportunity knocks just One time
Unforgettable
찾아낸 The right light
見つけ出した The right light
I found The right light
사라지지 않아
消えない
Won't go gentle into the night
눈에 새긴 One time
目に焼き付けた One time
Etched in my eyes One time
Unforgettable gettable gettable
One look give ‘em Whiplash whiplash
Beat drop with a big flash big flash
집중해 좀 더 Think fast Think fast
集中して もっと Think fast
C'mon, focus Think fast
이유 넌 이해 못 해
理由 君には分からない
They're reasons you'll never understand
왜 이제야
どうして今さら
Why at last
Know I did that did that
Day 1 know I been bad been bad
Don’t stop 흔들린 채
Don’t stop 揺さぶられたまま
Don’t stop Still shook
무리해도
無理しても
Goin' too hard, yet
Can’t touch that Can't touch that
I’m the highlight
비춰 Red light
照らす Red light
Shine the Red light
Yeah Tonight, it's all about me
You know it’s my site
거친 Next sigh
荒い Next sigh
Next sigh so heavy
만들어갈 History
作っていく History
We be writin' History
Ohhhhh
One look give ‘em Whiplash Whiplash
Beat drop with a big flash big flash
따라와 어서 Move fast Move fast
ついてきて 早く Move fast
C'mon keep up, Move fast
이유 넌 이해 못 해
理由 君には分からない
They're reasons you'll never understand
왜 이제야
どうして今さら
Why at last
Know I did that did that
Day 1 know I been bad been bad
Don’t stop 흔들린 채
Don’t stop 揺さぶられたまま
Don’t stop Still shook
다가와도
近づいてきても
Even it be incomin'
Can’t touch that Can’t touch that
Whip-Whiplash
One look give ‘em Whiplash